export const dentistry2 = [
  {
    question: "Dental enamel is:",
    options: {
      a: "Sensitive to weather changes",
      b: "Consists predominantly of water",
      c: "The hardest tissue in the human body",
    },
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Which microorganism is responsible for dental caries?",
    options: {
      a: "Streptococcus mutans",
      b: "Aggregatibacter actinomycetemcomitans",
      c: "Escherichia colli",
    },
    correct_answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Dental prosthetics is dealing with:",
    options: {
      a: "Treatment of periodontal diseases",
      b: "Restoration of missing teeth and dental arches",
      c: "Treatment of disorders of dental pulp",
    },
    correct_answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Temporary (decidual) dentition consists of:",
    options: {
      a: "Incisors + 1 canine + 2 molars",
      b: "Incisors + 1 canine + 1 premolar + 1 molar",
      c: "Incisors + 1 canine + 2 premolars + 3 molars",
    },
    correct_answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Predisposing factor of periodontal diseases is:",
    options: {
      a: "Drinking of water with low pH",
      b: "Eating of vegetarian food",
      c: "Poor oral hygiene",
    },
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Average number of movements in temporomandibular joint is:",
    options: {
      a: "20-30 times a day",
      b: "2-3 million times a day",
      c: "2,000-3,000 times a day",
    },
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "How many dentitions are described in humans?",
    options: {
      a: "One in males and two in females",
      b: "Three â€“ in early age, in middle age, and in senium",
      c: "Two - temporary and permanent",
    },
    correct_answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Treatment of oral cancer is:",
    options: {
      a: "Based on combination of surgical treatment, radiotherapy, and chemotherapy",
      b: "Based on bone marrow transplantation",
      c: "Possible only in advanced stages, early stages of the disease are not treated",
    },
    correct_answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Most common site of facial fracture is:",
    options: {
      a: "Upper third",
      b: "Middle third",
      c: "Lower third",
    },
    correct_answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Most frequent type of malignant tumor in the oral cavity is:",
    options: {
      a: "Squamous cell cancer",
      b: "Osteosarcoma",
      c: "Pleomorphic adenoma",
    },
    correct_answer: "a",
  },
];
